[
    {
      "question": " (1015)2 = ? ",
      "choice1": "1030225",
      "choice2": "1030125",
      "choice3": "1032225",
      "choice4": "1130225",
      "answer": 1
    },
      {
        "question": "Largest five digit number exactly divisible by 39 is:",
        "choice1": "99696",
        "choice2": "99666",
        "choice3": "99986",
        "choice4": "99996",
        "answer": 4
      },
      {
        "question": "A speedboat runs 6 km upstream in a river and comes back to the starting point in 33 minutes. The stream of the river is running at 2 km/hr. What is the speed of speedboat in still water?",
        "choice1": "20 km/h",
        "choice2": "22 km/h",
        "choice3": "21 km/h",
        "choice4": "24 km/h",
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "A boat runs at the speed of 13 km/h in still water. If the speed of the stream is 4 km/h, how much time will it take to go 68 km downstream?",
        "choice1": "13 h",
        "choice2": "9 h",
        "choice3": "5 h",
        "choice4": "4 h",
        "answer": 4
      },
      {
        "question": "A motorboat crosses a certain distance in 1 hour and comes back in 1½ hours. If the stream is running at 3 km/h, find out the speed of motorboat in still water.",
        "choice1": "14",
        "choice2": "10",
        "choice3": "15",
        "choice4": "12",
        "answer": 3
      },
      {
        "question": " In a certain code, HARYANA is written as 8197151, how is DELHI written in that code?",
        "choice1": "45289",
        "choice2": "45389",
        "choice3": "45359",
        "choice4": "45689",
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "question": " In a certain code, NEWYORK is written as 111, how is NEWJERSEY written in that code?",
        "choice1": "123",
        "choice2": "114",
        "choice3": "124",
        "choice4": "108",
        "answer": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "In a clock, the time is 3.25.What is the angle between the hour hand and the minute hand of the clock:",
        "choice1": "95/2 degrees",
        "choice2": "94/3 degrees",
        "choice3": "90/3 degrees",
        "choice4": "95/3 degrees",
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "A clock gains uniformly 5 min slow at 8 o’clock in the morning on Sunday and 5 min 48 sec fast at 8 pm on following Sunday. The correct time and day are:",
        "choice1": "20 min past 7 pm and Wednesday",
        "choice2": "20 min past 7 pm and Thursday",
        "choice3": "21 min past 7 pm and Wednesday",
        "choice4": "21 min past 7 pm and Thursda",
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "The time of a clock is 8 am. Suddenly the clock gains 10 minutes in 24 hours. Find out the original time if the time of the clock is 1 pm on the following day:",
        "choice1": "48 minutes past 11",
        "choice2": "47 minutes past 10",
        "choice3": "48 minutes past 09",
        "choice4": "48 minutes past 12",
        "answer": 4
      },
      {
        "question": "If tan (x+y) tan (x-y) = 1, then find tan (2x/3)?",
        "choice1": "1/2",
        "choice2": "1/√3",
        "choice3": "1/√2",
        "choice4": "2/√3",
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "A boatman takes 3 hours 45 minutes to travel 15 km downstream and takes 2 hours 30 minutes to travel 5 km upstream of a river. What is the speed of the stream of the river in km/h?",
        "choice1": "4 km/h",
        "choice2": "2 km/h",
        "choice3": "6 km/h",
        "choice4": "1 km/h",
        "answer": 4
      }
    ]